Hi, Annie! We made you this video to celebrate you becoming a voter!
Mazelto! We remembered how much you loved that video that we made you you know
with your friends and your family for your botnitzva, which was so amazing.
So your mom sent an email to your aunt and uncle and your cousins, your sister.
I'm gonna see it, Marty. Alright, watch the video. Watch it, we worked hard.
It's fun.
Hey, Annie! Um, mom told me that you'd be celebrating your mitzvot this
November and that I should record something for you. Actually, mom was really
freaking out about this. Told her she used to meditate.
Voting for the first time. That can be intimidating, but don't worry.
There are a ton of old people there. So if you have any questions, they got you.
Happy mitzvot! Hala!
Hala! It's grandma and grandpa. The first time I voted was in 1948.
Truman was running against Dewey. On election day, the newspapers all thought Dewey
had won, so they printed it to Hazel. Dewey defeats Truman!
Oh! Truman had won! That was fake news!
You're not, Hala.
You're great grandfather, didn't vote in the 1933 elections.
In Germany. Big mistake.
We're so proud that you're voting this year, Hanna.
Love you, boomerang!
I don't know which button. I don't know either.
Hanna! This is Shira, your favorite madreja from Crane Lake Camp.
Congrats on your mitzvot! I'm so proud of you.
Shalom, Hanna!
Whoa! It's your old friend, Rabbi Ruth.
As you know from Hebrew school, according to Jewish tradition,
there are 613 mitzvot or obligations.
I have always considered voting to be the 614th mitzvot.
And to be honest, some of the original 613 aren't so useful.
I mean, do I really need to be told not to have sex with my in-laws?
I don't think so. Ew, we get it, Hachem.
May your first vote be a blessed one.
Lahiam!
Yo, Hanna, Sam here.
Hanna, what up?
That's Doug. We're tight with your parents.
Do you remember meeting us when you were little?
I know we have an age watch.
Which one is she?
She's the second favorite.
Oh, yeah. Hanna, you're turning 18
and you're celebrating your mitzvot.
This is epic.
I remember my first time like it was yesterday.
It was yesterday, sick burn.
You should be open to all types of political experiences.
Don't be afraid to play the field.
For a governor, you could vote for Congress.
Play on, player.
I really need to make new friends.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Hanna, Hanna.
Happy mitzvot.
Voting is learned.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, yeah.
And remember that a hundred years ago, we weren't even allowed to vote.
That's right. That's why we named you after Hanna Aaron
to do a thing or two about important elections.
That's true. I need you after my great-grandmother, Kanna.
Well, she was a wonderful person.
I didn't know her, obviously.
But as Beyonce said, girls, who runs this mother,
who runs the world, girls.